

Typescript, Javascript, C#, ReasonML, Swift, Python, Java, Kotlin, C++, Objective-C

<u> tarasvozniuk@microsoft.com</u>

Taiwan

github.com/ambientlight

→ tarasvozniuk.com

stackoverflow.com/users/2380455

in linkedin.com/in/tarasvozniuk/

SUMMARY

Seasoned engineer currently working as part of MSFT Bing mobile team. My previous experience involved working on various map interactions and tooling. I am overall very fortunate to have worked in various domains including mobile development, full-stack, cloud architecture, devops as well as deep learning.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Software Engineer, Bing Mobile

Microsoft | Taiwan | Aug 2023 - Present

- Role can be described as E2E jack-of-all-trades work where architecture level improvements and optimizations are made
- Primarily focused on native iOS / Android development as well as some frontend work (webviews/typescript)

Senior Software Engineer, Azure Maps

Microsoft | Taiwan | Mar 2022 - Jul 2023

Software Engineer II, Azure Maps

Microsoft | Taiwan | Apr 2021 - Feb 2022

Primary developer of Azure Maps Web, Android, iOS SDKs, my contribution also included REST SDKs, architecture and devops.

Lead Developer, Software Architect

GeoThings | Taiwan | Aug 2017 - Apr 2021

- Designed and built a scalable cloud-native infrastructure for our service on AWS utilizing lambdas & ECS behind ALB, aurora postgres, redis, S3 behind CloudFront CDN as we migrated our legacy infra from Azure.
- Made large-scale data collection possible by designing and building machine learning pipeline capable of extracting roadside objects with its locations from windshield cam videos by using YoloV3 for object detection and deep-sort for tracking.
- Helped achieving 99.9% uptime by providing almost 24x7 response rate (vocations included) for critical fixes and infrastructure issues
- Lead developer of our frontend and backend stacks

iOS Developer

GeoThings | Taiwan | Sep 2015 - Aug 2017

- Primarily developed map-centric application on top of WhirlyGlobe-Maply and later MapboxGL
- Enabled survey collection in remote areas by building an offline-oriented location-based survey collection app in swift
- Wrote a number of data crawlers to collect disaster-related open data (like typhoon dujuan)

iOS Developer

Sixnology | Taiwan | Apr 2013 - Aug 2014

Built DLNA-complient audio streaming player for iOS supporting media from local library, UPNP Media Servers, and Spotify.

RECOGNITIONS

Winners - NCTU Seed Fund Competition: NCTU Startup Lab | Nov 2018

Inside the winning batch of NCTU entrepreneurial competition $\label{eq:ncture} % \begin{center} \begin{center$

Best Potential Team Award - Beyond Future Mobility: MIT Media Lab X NCTU | Sept 2015

- Gathered a team of talented folks to build a personal flying assistant helium drone
- Won best potential team award among 31 teams participating in the workshop by demonstrating our prototype and the validity of our idea

EDUCATION

National Chiao Tung University | earned Jun 2015

Double Degree: B.S. Computer Science, B.S. Finance & Information Management

STACKS

react, angular, react-native, electron, django, aws amplify, serverless, aws lambda, cloudformation, docker, aws ecs, kubernetes, postgresql, dynamodb, sqlite, neo4j, redis, realm, redux, rxjs, graphql, logux, pixijs, jest, selenium, webpack, fastlane, bitrise, githubactions, keras tensorflow, opencv

OPEN SOURCE CONTRIBUTIONS

ReKotlin, AWS Amplify, tilequeue, reductive-dev-tools, reductive-observable, amplify-cli-action, bs-rx, GithubIssuesExtension